The Beach House is a tv movie, romance, drama film
directed by Roger Spottiswoode.
Cara Rudland thought she’d left her Southern roots and troubled family far behind, but returns to
the scenic Lowcountry of her childhood summers after losing her job in Chicago.
There, she reconnects with her mother Lovie, who has been caring for her
young, pregnant friend Toy in her charming beach house.
Coretta 'Cara' Rudland, played by Minka Kelly.
Brett Beauchamps, played by Chad Michael Murray.
Lovie Rudland, played by Andie MacDowell.
Toy, played by Makenzie Vega.
Flo, played by Donna Biscoe.
Palmer Rudland, played by Donny Boaz.
The Beach House is a 2018 American made-for-television drama film directed by
Roger Spottiswoode based on the 2002 novel by Mary Alice Monroe.
It stars Minka Kelly, Andie MacDowell, Chad Michael
Murray, Donna Biscoe and Makenzie Vega.
Returning to her family beach house upon her mother Lovie's request, Caretta plans
to soon return to Chicago until unexpected events change her mind.
The film explores themes of small town, beach, based on
novel or book, roommates, ex-boyfriend.
The tone is emotional.